RG 044, Office of Health Care Access
Connecticut State Library
Office of Health Care Access records
1973-1998,
bulk 1983-1993
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. Office of Health Care Access
107 cubic feet
The Office of Health Care Access was established in 1994 to ensure that the citizens of Connecticut have access to a quality health care delivery system.
RG044
2003-025
Historical Note
The Office of Health Care Access was established in 1994 to ensure that the citizens of Connecticut have access to a quality health care delivery system. It was restructured in 1995 as a sucessor to the Commission on Hospitals and Health Care.
Scope and Content
This record group includes declaratory rulings and meeting packets. Declaratory rulings consist of chronological, budget, and rate order final decisions. Meeting packets consist of agendas, minutes, and calendars.
Arrangement
Series 1. Declaratory Rulings, 1975-1998, Accession 2003-025
Boxes listed as recieved from the agency.
Series 2. Meeting packets, 1973-1995, Accession 2003-025
Boxes listed as recieved from the agency.
Related Material
None.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. Office of Health Care Access
Subjects:
Connecticut. Office of Health Care Access -- Records and correspondence; Health services accessibility -- Connecticut; Medical care -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Agendas; Calendars; Correspondence; Minutes; Reports
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Series 1. Declaratory Rulings, 1975-1998
  - Chronological final decisions
    - 1983 January-1984 May (Box 1)
    - Long Forms, 1984 (Box 2)
    - 1984 May 21-December 4 (Box 3)
    - 1984 December 11-30, 1985 January 2-March 19 (Box 4)
    - 1985 March 26-September 10 (Box 5)
    - 1985 September 17 (Box 7)
    - 1986 January 3-August 14 (Box 8)
    - 1986 August 14 (Box 9)
    - 1987 January 8-April 13 (Box 10)
    - 1987 April 14-July 14 (Box 11)
    - 1987 July 21-October 14 (Box 12)
    - 1987 October 20-November 10 (Box 13)
    - 1987 November 17-30 (Box 14)
    - 1987 November 30-December 30 (Box 15)
    - 1988 January 5-19 (Box 16)
    - 1988 April 21-August 16 (Box 17)
    - 1988 August 16-September 19 (Box 18)
    - 1988 September 20-December 2 (Box 19)
    - 1989 January 4-June 27 (Box 20)
    - 1989 July 5-December 29 (Box 21)
    - 1990 January 10-December 21 (Box 22)
    - 1990 July 17-October 5 (Box 23)
    - 1991 April 2-July 11 (Box 24)
    - 1991 July 18-October 10 (Box 25)
    - 1991 November 21-December 19 (Box 26)
    - 1991 October 11-November 14 (Box 27)
    - 1992 January 1-May 31 (Box 28)
    - 1992 May 28-September 3 (Box 29)
    - 1992 September 10-24 (Box 30)
    - 1992 September 24-October 1 (Box 31)
    - 1992 October 8-December 30 (Box 32)
    - 1993 January-July (Box 33)
    - 1994 January 3-June 23 (Box 34)
    - 1994 June 23-September 29 (Box 35)
    - 1995 January 5-June 1 (Box 36)
    - 1995 June 1-September 28 (Box 37)
    - 1995 September 28-December 28 (Box 38)
    - 1996 January 4-August 14 (Box 39)
  - 500s Final decisions, 1978-1981 (Box 40)
  - Long term care final decisions, 1975-1983 (Box 41)
  - Assisted Living Services Agencies (ALSAs), 1995-1998 (Box 41)
  - Specialty and psychiatric final decisions, 1979-1987 (Box 42)
  - Acute care final decisions (500s), 1982-1983 (Box 42)
  - Rate order final decisions, 1979-1980 (Box 43)
  - Rate order final decisions, 1980-1982 (Box 44)
  - Rate order final decisions and master books, 1980-1982 (Box 45)
  - Compliance final decisions, 1981-1985 (Box 46)
  - Long term care final decisions, 1983-1985 (Box 47)
  - Final decisions, Backus - WWII, 1983 (Box 48)
  - Acute care decisions and EPEA budgets, 1984 (Box 49)
  - Budget final decisions, 1985 (Box 50)
  - Budget final decisiosn, Backus - St. Mary's, 1986 (Box 51)
  - Budget final decisions, St. Raphael - Yale, 1986 (Box 52)
  - Compliance final decisions, 1987 (Box 53)
  - Final decisions, Backus - Milford, 1987 (Box 54)
  - Final decisions, Norwalk - Yale, 1987 (Box 55)
  - Compliance final decisions, 1987 (Box 56)
  - Rate order final decisions, St. Mary's - Yale, 1988 (Box 57)
  - Compliance final decisions, 1988 (Box 58)
  - Rate orders, Backus - Lawrence & Memorial, 1988 (Box 59)
  - Final decisions, Manchester - St. Joseph, 1988 (Box 60)
  - Rate order final decisions, Greenwich - Park City, 1989 (Box 61)
  - Rate order final decisions, Rockville, Stamford, Waterbury, 1989 (Box 62)
  - Rate order final decisions, Backus - Charlotte Hungerford, 1989 (Box 63)
  - Rate order final decisions, Veterans - Yale, 1989 (Box 64)
  - Budget final decisions, 1990 (Box 65)
  - Psychiatric & specialty hospitals 90-915, 1990 (Box 66)
  - Budget final decisions, Backus - Yale, 1991 (Box 67)
  - Budget final decisions, Windham - Yale, 1992 (Box 68)
  - Final decisions, New Britain General - Waterbury, 1992 (Box 69)
  - Budget final decisions, Backus - mt. Sinai, 1992 (Box 70)
  - Compliance final decisions, Backus - Yale, 1992 (Box 71)
  - Home Health, 1993 (Box 73)
  - Compliance final decisions, 1993 (Box 74)
  - Rate order final decisions, Backus - New Milford, 1993 (Box 75)
  - Rate order final decisions, Rockville - Yale, 1993 (Box 76)
  - CON Determinations, 1994 (Box 77)
  - Rate order decisions, 1994 (Box 78)
  - Rate order final decisions, Middlesex - New Milford, 1994 (Box 79)
  - Psychiatric, 94-906 - 94-925Ra, 1994 (Box 80)
  - Rate order final decisions, Griffin - Manchester, 1994 (Box 81)
  - Chronological final decisions, Backus - St. Joseph, 1996 (Box 82)
  - Chronological final decisiosn, 1991 April 2-July 11 (Box 83)
  - Home Health Agency (HHA), 1990 (Box 84)
  - Restricted funds, 1985 (Box 84)
- Series 2. Meeting packets, 1973-1995
  - Agendas, Calendars, Minutes, 1993-1995 (Box 84)
  - Agendas, Calendars, Minutes, 1990-1993 (Box 85)
  - Agendas, Calendars, Minutes, 1973-1982 (Box 86)
  - UCP meeting notes and final decisions, 1992 (Box 87)
  - Agendas, Calendars, Secretary of State, Minutes, 1983-1986 (Box 88)
  - Agendas, Calendars, Secretary of State, Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 88)
  - Commission on Hospitals and Health Care meeting folders (Box 89)
    - 1988 October 6-1989 February 28 (Box 90)
    - 1988 September 19 (Box 91)
    - 1991 February 5-August 1 (Box 92)
    - 1988 April 26-September 27 (Box 93)
    - 1992 September 1-October 29 (Box 94)
    - 1988 October 6-1989 February 28 (Box 95)
    - 1994 October 4-1995 June 30 (Box 96)
    - 1987 December 1-1988 April 19 (Box 97)
    - 1995 June 1 (Box 98)
    - 1989 March 7-October 27 (Box 99)
    - 1991 August 15-December 27 (Box 100)
    - 1987 July 7-October 20 (Box 101)
    - 1992 March 5-August 27 (Box 102)
    - 1993 November 4-June 23 (Box 103)
    - 1987 October 22-November 19 (Box 104)
    - 1987 November 19-30 (Box 105)
    - 1990 July 21-1991 January 29 (Box 106)
    - 1994 June 30-September 29 (Box 107)
    - 1993 July 1-October 21 (Box 108)